# **Probo Krishnacahya**

## Frontend Developer, UI/UX Designer



probo.krishnacahya@gmail.com



https://probo-krishnacahya.web.app/



#### **About Me**

I am proficient in Frontend Development and UI/UX Design with 2+ years of experience in creating visually pleasing and user-friendly designs while prioritizing accessibility. Along with that, Cooperative Teamwork, Proactive, Persistence, Lifelong Learner, and High Sense of Achievement defines my main qualities.

### **Professional Experiences**

#### **Corporate Entrepreneurship Implementation Student Assistant**

Universitas Ciputra Surabaya September 2023 - January 2024

#### **UI/UX Designer, iOS Developer Intern**

Apple Developer Academy @ UC March 2023 - December 2023

#### **Digital Entrepreneurship and Innovation Student Assistant**

Universitas Ciputra Surabaya February 2023 - June 2023

#### **Web Development Lecturer Research Assistant**

Universitas Ciputra Surabaya August 2022 - January 2023

#### **Educations**

#### **Universitas Ciputra Surabaya**

Sarjana Komputer, Informatika 2020 - 2024

#### SMA Kristen Dharma Mulya Surabaya

Ilmu Pengetahuan Sosial 2017 - 2020

_		
•	<i>-</i>	
	kil	15

SwiftUI	••••
ReactJS	••••
Flutter	••••
Figma	••••
Sketch	••••

#### Languages

Indonesian **English** Chinese

#### Volunteering

#### **Bebras Indonesia Computational Thinking** Challenge 2022

Member of UC Bureau Committee November 2022 - January 2023

#### **Best Practices on Computational Thinking** for Future Educators Workshop 2022

Member of Module Division July 2022 - September 2022

### **Technopreneurship Workshop 2022**

Member of IT - Inventory Division **April 2022** 

## 8<sup>th</sup> National Programming & Logic **Competition 2021**

Member of Marketing Division November 2020 - January 2021

#### **Awards**

### 7<sup>th</sup> Place - Informatics Festival and **Competition 2023 (UI/UX Design)**

Universitas Udayana Badung October 2023

### 2<sup>nd</sup> Place - Lomba Nasional Kreativitas Mahasiswa 2022 (Web/Mobile Application)

Asosiasi Perguruan Tinggi Swasta Indonesia Wilayah VII Jawa Timur November 2022

## 2<sup>nd</sup> Place - National Informatic Fun **Competition 2K22 (UI/UX Design)**

Universitas Muhammadiyah Riau August 2022

## 9<sup>th</sup> Place - Faculty of Information **Technology Competition 2022 (Web Developer**)

Universitas Kristen Satya Wacana Salatiga August 2022